<resources xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0802_00_Magistrate" speaker="Magistrate Redridge" name="MagistrateRedridge" VO="0802_00_Magistrate_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Hello, dearie, and welcome to Ebonscale Reach. Constance Redridge, at your service.\n\nI assure you, we are doing everything we can to battle against the Corruption here.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0802_01_Magistrate" speaker="Magistrate Redridge" name="MagistrateRedridge" VO="0802_01_Magistrate_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Welcome to Ebonscale Reach, dearie. I'm Constance Redridge.\n\nThe Corrupted threat has finally attracted the attention of the rest of Aeternum, but we've been keenly aware of it for years.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0802_02_Magistrate" speaker="Magistrate Redridge" name="MagistrateRedridge" VO="0802_02_Magistrate_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">It's my fervent belief that canceling our cultural traditions puts us in the mentality of defeat.\n\nBut we must ensure the Corrupted don't interrupt our performance. They will try if they learn of it.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0802_03_Magistrate" speaker="Magistrate Redridge" name="MagistrateRedridge" VO="0802_03_Magistrate_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Thank you for all your help, dearie. Rehearsals of our play are going smoothly once more.\n\nI will let you know once we've scheduled a performance.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0803_00_Survivalist" speaker="Survivalist Hopkins" name="SurvivalistHopkins" VO="0803_00_Survivalist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">If you're the hunting type, you'll find Ebonscale has a variety of wildlife unlike anywhere else on Aeternum.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0803_01_Survivalist" speaker="Survivalist Hopkins" name="SurvivalistHopkins" VO="0803_01_Survivalist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Ah, I think I've spotted a fellow hunter of beasts, have I not?\n\nThe creatures here in Ebonscale are the most dangerous in all of Aeternum, a fine challenge if you've the gall to accept it.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0803_02_Survivalist" speaker="Survivalist Hopkins" name="SurvivalistHopkins" VO="0803_02_Survivalist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Well now, you've proven yourself adept at hunting a type of creature you're likely familiar with.\n\nWhat would you say to taking on even more thrilling challenge? What would you say to hunting tigers?</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0803_03_Survivalist" speaker="Survivalist Hopkins" name="SurvivalistHopkins" VO="0803_03_Survivalist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I tip my skinning knife to you, friend. You've got serious skill with besting beasts.\n\nPerhaps someday, when this Corruption business abates, we can go on an expedition together.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0804_00_Overseer" speaker="Elder Danya" name="OverseerSolomon" VO="0804_00_Overseer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">You are new to Ebonscale, but I see potential in you already.\n\nThere are always opportunities to improve life here in the settlement.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0804_01_Overseer" speaker="Elder Danya" name="OverseerSolomon" VO="0804_01_Overseer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Ah, it is good to have you here in our fine settlement.\n\nDid you wash ashore in Ebonscale, or have you come from some other part of the island?</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0804_02_Overseer" speaker="Elder Danya" name="OverseerSolomon" VO="0804_02_Overseer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Now, to slightly less enjoyable subject - the catastrophic flooding of the southern plains. \n\nMany people seemed to have been killed -  we put their corpses in the Skysong Crypt, but in the end, they did not stay dead.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0804_03_Overseer" speaker="Elder Danya" name="OverseerSolomon" VO="0804_03_Overseer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Your services to the settlement and the people in it shall not be soon forgotten.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0805_00_Artificer" speaker="Artificer Long" name="ArtificerLong" VO="0805_00_Artificer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Greetings, I am Ting Long. I once served  the Zhou Dynasty, but I am now proudly independent.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0805_01_Artificer" speaker="Artificer Long" name="ArtificerLong" VO="0805_01_Artificer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">You come here to Ebonscale at the same time as the Corruption surges and envelops the land around us. \n\nHow do I know you aren't an agent of Corruption here to deceive me once again?</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0805_02_Artificer" speaker="Artificer Long" name="ArtificerLong" VO="0805_02_Artificer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I feel partly responsible for the damage the Empress and her Corrupted have wrought.\n\nAfter all, I helped build the shrines she leveraged for power. I cannot repair all the damage, but I would like to try.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0805_03_Artificer" speaker="Artificer Long" name="ArtificerLong" VO="0805_03_Artificer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Cleansing the Shrine will set the Empress and her forces back, but it will not stop them.\n\nThese plans you recovered indicate that even now, her lieutenants meet to plan an offensive.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0805_04_Artificer" speaker="Artificer Long" name="ArtificerLong" VO="0805_04_Artificer_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">For all you've done, you deserve my thanks and more. \n\nFor now, my work is redeemed and my heart is at peace, cleansed like the Dragon Shrine.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_00_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_00_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Keep lookin' at me like that and I'll make your jaw dance.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_01_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_01_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Always happy to see a fellow soldier-of-fortune. How can I help you, mate?</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_01pre_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_01_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Always happy to see a fellow soldier-of-fortune. How can I help you, mate?\n\n[ Level 49 required for Ebonscale Reach faction missions ]</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_02_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_02_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Go on, sling your hook, big brain. I've had my fill of your kind.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_03_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_03_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Here to offer me salvation?  I've got all the salvation I need in this here scabbard.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_04_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_04_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Well now, it's my honor to finally acknowledge the rising Champion in our ranks.\n\nMany have come forward to vouch for your valor, and now you are ready face the trial to become a Commander.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_04pre_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_04_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Well now, it's my honor to finally acknowledge the rising Champion in our ranks.\n\nMany have come forward to vouch for your valor, and now you are ready face the trial to become a Commander.\n\n[ Level 49 required for Ebonscale Reach faction missions ]</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_05_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_05_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I salute you, Commander {playerName}. You are a paragon within our ranks.\n\nBack to the fight, then! Always, to the fight!</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0807_05pre_Commander" speaker="Commander Hartford" name="CommanderHartford" VO="0807_05_Commander_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I salute you, Commander {playerName}. You are a paragon within our ranks.\n\nBack to the fight, then! Always, to the fight!\n\n[ Level 49 required for Ebonscale Reach faction missions ]</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0808_00_Alchemist" speaker="Alchemist Regis" name="AlchemistRegis" VO="0808_00_Alchemist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Good day, stranger. Make yourself at home here in Ebonscale Reach. I am Alchemist Lane.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0808_01_Alchemist" speaker="Alchemist Regis" name="AlchemistRegis" VO="0808_01_Alchemist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Seek forever farther, my scholar. In what manner may I oblige you?</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0808_01pre_Alchemist" speaker="Alchemist Regis" name="AlchemistRegis" VO="0808_01_Alchemist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Seek forever farther, my scholar. In what manner may I oblige you?\n\n[ Level 49 required for Ebonscale Reach faction missions ]</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0808_02_Alchemist" speaker="Alchemist Regis" name="AlchemistRegis" VO="0808_02_Alchemist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Ignorance is bold, knowledge is reserved. -Thucydides</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0808_03_Alchemist" speaker="Alchemist Regis" name="AlchemistRegis" VO="0808_03_Alchemist_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Many, while doing the foulest deeds, use the fairest words. -Democritus</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0809_00_Adjudicator" speaker="Adjudicator Wen" name="AdjudicatorWen" VO="0809_00_Adjudicator_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">May the light protect you. Adjudicator Wen at your service.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0809_01_Adjudicator" speaker="Adjudicator Wen" name="AdjudicatorWen" VO="0809_01_Adjudicator_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I welcome you in service to the light. What is your bidding, fellow keeper.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0809_01pre_Adjudicator" speaker="Adjudicator Wen" name="AdjudicatorWen" VO="0809_01_Adjudicator_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I welcome you in service to the light. What is your bidding, fellow keeper.\n\n[ Level 49 required for Ebonscale Reach faction missions ]</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0809_02_Adjudicator" speaker="Adjudicator Wen" name="AdjudicatorWen" VO="0809_02_Adjudicator_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">You may not recognize it, Marauder, but the light watches over even you.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0809_03_Adjudicator" speaker="Adjudicator Wen" name="AdjudicatorWen" VO="0809_03_Adjudicator_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I respect your hunger for knowledge, researcher. But the most important is found within, not without.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0810_00_Barkeep" speaker="Barkeep Bao" name="BarkeepBao" VO="0810_00_Barkeep_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Welcome to the Ebonscale Bar. I am Bao, and I serve food and drink here.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0810_01_Barkeep" speaker="Barkeep Bao" name="BarkeepBao" VO="0810_01_Barkeep_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Hello there! Are you new to Ebonscale Reach? Yes, I think so! \n\nThere are many curiosities here - the flora, the fauna, the very elements themselves - I believe this territory is unique!</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0810_02_Barkeep" speaker="Barkeep Bao" name="BarkeepBao" VO="0810_02_Barkeep_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Are you ready to get your hands dirty with another task of mine? This one will prove much more dangerous.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0810_03_Barkeep" speaker="Barkeep Bao" name="BarkeepBao" VO="0810_03_Barkeep_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">You've satisfied my many curiosities about the Reach we now call home and made it a safer place to be.\n\nYou have my eternal gratitude.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0811_00_Stranger" speaker="Zeng Lingyun" name="ZengLingyun" VO="0811_00_Stranger_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">You are most welcome to Ebonscale, traveler. \n\nDespite the dangers, I hope you can find some measure of peace and comfort here.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0811_01_Stranger" speaker="Zeng Lingyun" name="ZengLingyun" VO="0811_01_Stranger_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Greetings. It is a pleasure to meet you.\n\nI am Zeng Lingyun, former handmaiden to the Empress Zhou Taiying, before she became Corrupted.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0811_02_Stranger" speaker="Zeng Lingyun" name="ZengLingyun" VO="0811_02_Stranger_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">We have the statuettes now, and the key is assembled.\n\nNow, you may challenge the Empress and her Corrupted cohort.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0824_00_Innkeep" speaker="Innkeep Tamar" name="InnkeepTamar" VO="0824_00_Innkeep_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Come, rest your weary feet here at the Dark Night Inn.\n\nYou'll find no better rest in all Aeternum.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0823_00_Fisher" speaker="Master Fisher Chang" name="MasterFisherChang" VO="0823_00_Fisher_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I'm Master Fisher Chang and fishing is my game! I'm an expert on the fish in the area.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0823_01_Fisher" speaker="Master Fisher Chang" name="MasterFisherChang" VO="0823_01_Fisher_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I'm Master Fisher Chang and fishing is my game! I'm an expert on the fish in the area.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0823_02_Fisher" speaker="Master Fisher Chang" name="MasterFisherChang" VO="0823_02_Fisher_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">One day I'd like to start up a fishing tournament. Wouldn't that be splendid?</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0899_00_Liberator" speaker="Liberator Guo" name="LiberatorGuo" VO_Status="Needs Recording">I am here to loose the chains of all who would defy the Empress, for the good of the world.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0899_01_Liberator" speaker="Liberator Guo" name="LiberatorGuo" VO_Status="Needs Recording">My fighting prime may be long past, but I will never stop being Guo the Liberator. Wherever there is injustice, I appear.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0825_00_ShuSong" speaker="ShuSong Lin" name="ShuSongLin" VO_Status="Needs Recording">Is there nothing the Corrupted touch that they do not destroy? The pain of losing one to their ranks, I can't even imagine.\n\nBarkeep Bao is dealing with such loss, and all I want to do is make him a hot meal…</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0825_01_ShuSong" speaker="ShuSong Lin" name="ShuSongLin" VO_Status="Needs Recording">Oh, woe is me, the tools of my craft have been swarmed by the foul Corrupted.\n\nAdventurer, might you be willing to help a Culinarian in need?</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0825_02_ShuSong" speaker="ShuSong Lin" name="ShuSongLin" VO_Status="Needs Recording">For recovering my supplies you have my eternal gratitude, but I wonder if you would keep up your virtuous streak for another task?\n\nThe salted meats I collected for this special meal were eaten by the Corrupted forces.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0825_03_ShuSong" speaker="ShuSong Lin" name="ShuSongLin" VO_Status="Needs Recording">With the tools and meats recovered I can begin crafting this meal.\n\nHere, come closer, let me show you my techniques…</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0825_04_ShuSong" speaker="ShuSong Lin" name="ShuSongLin" VO_Status="Needs Recording">How did Bao find the cuisine? Was it a good reaction?\n\nI will venture to the settlement to speak with him about it… Eventually.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0826_00_MaWeizhe" speaker="Ma Weizhe" name="MaWeizhe" VO_Status="Needs Recording">Even the most innocent of animals are at risk of being Corrupted and turned into weapons.\n\nTigers--Tigers are another matter entirely.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0826_01_MaWeizhe" speaker="Ma Weizhe" name="MaWeizhe" VO_Status="Needs Recording">I have always had a soft spot for cats, especially the big ones.\n\nApparently this is also true of the Corrupted, for I know a place where they whelp tigers to corrupt for their twisted machinations.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0826_02_MaWeizhe" speaker="Ma Weizhe" name="MaWeizhe" VO_Status="Needs Recording">It warms my heart to see those tigers you freed growing up in the wilds around us. You did a good thing here, adventurer.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0827_00_Bardroy" speaker="Bardroy Betham" name="BardroyBetham" VO_Status="Needs Recording">Stranger, never have children. Even if it's near-impossible on this island to procreate I still feel it necessary to warn you.\n\nKids are nothing but trouble.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0827_01_Bardroy" speaker="Bardroy Betham" name="BardroyBetham" VO_Status="Needs Recording">The name's Bardroy Betham. My sons, Bartolome and Bartholomew, are driving me mad.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0827_02_Bardroy" speaker="Bardroy Betham" name="BardroyBetham" VO_Status="Needs Recording">Thanks again for teaching my boys a lesson in humility.\n\nTheir brains may be naught but barncales and sea rot now but I like to think you got a message through to them with the power of your attacks.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0828_00_YueLai" speaker="Yue Lai" name="YueLai" VO_Status="Needs Recording">I wonder… How similar to our homeland is this strange place? We have made Aeternum structures in our unique style, but I long to know more about China.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0828_01_YueLai" speaker="Yue Lai" name="YueLai" VO_Status="Needs Recording">I was but a babe when I was brought over on the ship from the Old World fleeing Shang Wu's forces.\n\nMy mother was an Empress loyalist until the floods and Corruption and whatnot. Still she doesn't like discussing our old home in China, where I was born.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0828_02_YueLai" speaker="Yue Lai" name="YueLai" VO_Status="Needs Recording">I want to know what was precious to my people before we had to deal with the rough wilderness of Aeternum. I saw some beautiful Heirlooms near the Dynasty Walls, but they are too well-guarded for me to reach.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0828_03_YueLai" speaker="Yue Lai" name="YueLai" VO_Status="Needs Recording">What are these characters…? Could that be…? My family name, Lai! Did we have a craftsperson in the family? Why wouldn't mother tell me this?</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0828_04_YueLai" speaker="Yue Lai" name="YueLai" VO_Status="Needs Recording">I am studying the artifacts my father crafted unbeknownst to mother. I do not wish to bring her pain, and will let her memories lie.\n\nI shall never stop seeking knowledge of my motherland.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0829_00_Enlai" speaker="Enlai Xiang" name="EnlaiXiang" VO_Status="Needs Recording">Ah, my dearest bride! Soon she and I shall be as one.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0829_01_Enlai" speaker="Enlai Xiang" name="EnlaiXiang" VO_Status="Needs Recording">Soon it shall be the dawn of the seventh day of the seventh month of the seventh year my love and I have been together… And I have nothing prepared for our wedding!</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0829_02_Enlai" speaker="Enlai Xiang" name="EnlaiXiang" VO_Status="Needs Recording">If you would hear one more request, there is the matter of the Red Strings of Fate my bride requested for our union.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0829_03_Enlai" speaker="Enlai Xiang" name="EnlaiXiang" VO_Status="Needs Recording">All of my wedding wishes have been fulfilled! You have earned my undying gratitude, friend.\n\nI can only hope you too find the happiness my bride and I have found, and that you get married some day too!</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0830_00_Posting" speaker="UI">WANTED: IVAN THE INEVITABLE</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0830_01_Posting" speaker="UI">WANTED: IVAN THE INEVITABLE\n\nBy order of Elder Danya of Ebonscale Reach, the graverobber-turned-lost behemoth of Ivan Monroe in the Skysong Crypt Church must be eliminated.</string>
	<string key="NPC_DefaultDialogue_0830_02_Posting" speaker="UI">(The board is now empty, free of wanted postings.)</string>
</resources>

