<resources xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<string key="1403_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_00_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Beware the Blight, stranger. The forests of Edengrove are hazardous enough during normal times.\n\nAnd to be clear, these are not normal times.</string>
	<string key="1403_02_DefaultDialogue" comment="to gates" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_01_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Welcome, brave one. Edengrove is a place of great beauty, but it's not for tourists.\n\nIt's one of the most deadly territories in Aeternum, especially now with the Blight having taken hold.</string>
	<string key="1403_03_DefaultDialogue" comment="gates to tincture" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_02_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I actually believed we made some diplomatic progress, before the Blight cropped up.\n\nIt threatens all life in Edengrove, human and Angry Earth alike.</string>
	<string key="1403_04_DefaultDialogue" comment="tincture to Blightpox" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_03_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">While you were mixing that tincture, I studied the samples you recovered.\n\nI begin to see a pattern, but I need to study an Angry Earth specimen that's resisted the Blight.</string>
	<string key="1403_05_DefaultDialogue" comment="pox to Blightstrength" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_04_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">You've been critical to my efforts thus far, though I know your true aim is to battle Corruption.\n\nI do believe this is all somehow related however, brave one, if you'll humor me.</string>
	<string key="1403_06_DefaultDialogue" comment="new loc" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_05_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I've only just arrived here. I need to get my bearings before I start work.\n\nI hope you'll excuse me, for the moment, at least.</string>
	<string key="1403_07_DefaultDialogue" comment="strength to migration" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_06_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I studied the samples you brought me for hours, trying to force them to make sense. I had a revelation!\n\nI believe I finally understand the Blight's origins, and perhaps its ultimate purpose.</string>
	<string key="1403_08_DefaultDialogue" comment="post migration" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_07_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I believe our work together has yielded great benefits, brave one.\n\nTogether, perhaps we can turn the tide against the Blight and this foul Corruption.</string>
	<string key="1403_09_DefaultDialogue" comment="GKW" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_08_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">The Blight may be as much a blessing as a curse, but it's still a threat, particularly to the Angry Earth.\n\nIt seems it has even reached the Garden of Genesis.</string>
	<string key="1403_10_DefaultDialogue" comment="post GKW" speaker="Survivalist Ellwood - Edengrove" name="SurvivalistEllwood" VO="1403_Survivalist_09_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I have great hope that what we've accomplished by restoring the Garden of Genesis will mean great things in the future.\n\nBe well, brave one.</string>
	<string key="1407_00_DefaultDialogue" speaker="Commander Hakim - Edengrove" name="CommanderHakim" gender="M" VO_Status="Not Recorded">You should have chosen the Marauders, friend. Unless you happen to like being chained down. Some people do.</string>
	<string key="1407_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="Marauder Member" speaker="Commander Hakim - Edengrove" name="CommanderHakim" gender="M" VO_Status="Not Recorded">Hey, pal. I can tell just by looking that you're a person who appreciates life's true joys. That's why you're a Marauder.</string>
	<string key="1407_01pre_DefaultDialogue" comment="Marauder Member" speaker="Commander Hakim - Edengrove" name="CommanderHakim" gender="M" VO_Status="Not Recorded">Hey, pal. I can tell just by looking that you're a person who appreciates life's true joys. That's why you're a Marauder.\n\n[ Level 49 required for Edengrove faction missions ]</string>
	<string key="1408_00_DefaultDialogue" speaker="Alchemist Zhi - Edengrove" name="AlchemistZhi" gender="F" VO_Status="Not Recorded">Oh, you're not in the Syndicate? I think I'm supposed to shun you. Yeah, I think I remember that from orientation.</string>
	<string key="1408_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="Syndicate Member" speaker="Alchemist Zhi - Edengrove" name="AlchemistZhi" gender="F" VO_Status="Not Recorded">When we pull together, we can do anything! We're the Syndicate!</string>
	<string key="1408_01pre_DefaultDialogue" comment="Syndicate Member" speaker="Alchemist Zhi - Edengrove" name="AlchemistZhi" gender="F" VO_Status="Not Recorded">When we pull together, we can do anything! We're the Syndicate!\n\n[ Level 49 required for Edengrove faction missions ]</string>
	<string key="1409_00_DefaultDialogue" speaker="Adjudicator Hansen - Edengrove" name="AdjudicatorHansen" gender="M" VO_Status="Not Recorded">You know, it's not too late for you. It's never too late to embrace the light of the Spark.</string>
	<string key="1409_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="Covenant Member" speaker="Adjudicator Hansen - Edengrove" name="AdjudicatorHansen" gender="M" VO_Status="Not Recorded">What? Oh, hello. I assume you're here to embrace your sacred duty to the Covenant? Good, good.</string>
	<string key="1409_01pre_DefaultDialogue" comment="Covenant Member" speaker="Adjudicator Hansen - Edengrove" name="AdjudicatorHansen" gender="M" VO_Status="Not Recorded">What? Oh, hello. I assume you're here to embrace your sacred duty to the Covenant? Good, good.\n\n[ Level 49 required for Edengrove faction missions ]</string>
	<string key="1416_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Warden Ducquet - Edengrove" name="WardenDucquet" VO="1416_Warden_00_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Well now, I hope you haven't come to Edengrove to enjoy the seasonal foliage.\n\nThis is not a season for such pleasures.</string>
	<string key="1416_02_DefaultDialogue" comment="to sabotage" speaker="Warden Ducquet - Edengrove" name="WardenDucquet" VO="1416_Warden_01_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Always good to see a fellow Warden walk through those gates.\n\nWe've been watching the Corrupted make advances into the forest, but we've yet to stop them.</string>
	<string key="1416_03_DefaultDialogue" comment="sabotage to foreman" speaker="Warden Ducquet - Edengrove" name="WardenDucquet" VO="1416_Warden_02_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">My hope is that we hit these crimson-eyed bastards so hard that THEY have nightmares about US.\n\nWhat do you say we take down their leaders?</string>
	<string key="1416_04_DefaultDialogue" comment="post foreman" speaker="Warden Ducquet - Edengrove" name="WardenDucquet" VO="1416_Warden_03_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Oh yes, I'm already hearing reports of the Corrupted withdrawing from some sectors.\n\nWay to show them what for, Warden! You've turned things around.</string>
	<string key="1418_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Ranger Wardell - Edengrove" name="RangerWardell" VO="1418_Ranger_00_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">If you have no business with me, then move along.</string>
	<string key="1418_02_DefaultDialogue" comment="lights" speaker="Ranger Wardell - Edengrove" name="RangerWardell" VO="1418_Ranger_01_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I know the Soulwardens are here because of the Corrupted.\n\nBut you should also know that here, perhaps more than other places, the Ancient Guardians are a threat as well.</string>
	<string key="1418_03_DefaultDialogue" comment="lights to azure tears" speaker="Ranger Wardell - Edengrove" name="RangerWardell" VO="1418_Ranger_02_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Unlike these other Wardens, you've proven that you're not just here to battle the Corrupted. There are many threats to humankind.\n\nPerhaps that means it's safe to share some of the Rangers' secrets with you.</string>
	<string key="1418_04_DefaultDialogue" comment="tears to northeast" speaker="Ranger Wardell - Edengrove" name="RangerWardell" VO="1418_Ranger_03_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">The Survivalist, Ellwood, made mention of your bravery. \n\nIt seems he's taken such a shine to you that he left a message for you when he left.</string>
	<string key="1418_05_DefaultDialogue" comment="post northeast" speaker="Ranger Wardell - Edengrove" name="RangerWardell" VO="1418_Ranger_04_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">The Rangers will always be at your back, even if you turn and see nothing.</string>
	<string key="1418_06_DefaultDialogue" comment="intro to RD" speaker="Ranger Wardell - Edengrove" name="RangerWardell" VO="1418_Ranger_05_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I heard about what you achieved with Madaki, you know.\n\nShe even sent me some of the designs to decrypt - an impenetrable Tower Shield, in fact.</string>
	<string key="1419_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Ranger Herb - Edengrove" name="RangerHerb" VO="1419_Ranger_00_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Though the forest is sacred to both the Angry Earth and the Rangers, it is no crime to chop down a tree.</string>
	<string key="1419_02_DefaultDialogue" comment="reformation" speaker="Ranger Herb - Edengrove" name="RangerHerb" VO="1419_Ranger_01_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Ah, you are the one who decrypted the Corrrupted's weapon recipes with Ranger Madaki.\n\nI was actually able to translate the formulation for a massive Greataxe.</string>
	<string key="1420_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Ranger Nagelhout - Edengrove" name="RangerNagelhout" VO="1420_Ranger_00_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">There is no natural system more complex nor more mysterious than the human mind.</string>
	<string key="1420_02_DefaultDialogue" comment="clamorous vox" speaker="Ranger Nagelhout - Edengrove" name="RangerNagelhout" VO="1420_Ranger_01_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">As much as I have a deep appreciation for nature, I believe human ingenuity is a miracle in its own right.\n\nThink of all we've accomplished across history. It's magnificent.</string>
	<string key="1421_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Ranger Chapman - Edengrove" name="RangerChapman" VO="1421_Ranger_00_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I've walked this territory for more years than I can count, but I've never seen the Grove in such chaos. Be careful as you wander this place.</string>
	<string key="1421_02_DefaultDialogue" comment="torrent" speaker="Ranger Chapman - Edengrove" name="RangerChapman" VO="1421_Ranger_01_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">You're the one who's worked with Madaki, aren't you?\n\nYes, I've heard all about you. I also managed to discover a design for a legendary bow, if you're interested.</string>
	<string key="1412_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Watcher Waters - Edengrove" name="WatcherWaters" VO="1412_01_INIT_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I've heard this place was the seed of all life on Earth, that it was a paradise at some point.\n\nDangerous as it may be, I think I kinda get that.</string>
	<string key="1413_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Watcher Lin - Edengrove" name="WatcherLin" VO="1413_01_INIT_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">You want to know what I think? I think the Angry Earth are just biding their time.\n\nSoon as we defeat the Corruption, they'll come for us. I trust these tree-things any farther than I can throw 'em.</string>
	<string key="1413_02_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Watcher Lin - Edengrove" name="WatcherLin" VO_Status="Not Recorded">Survivalist Ellwood is telling everyone now that the Angry Earth can help fight the Corruption, and the Rangers actually seem to be falling for it!\n\nNo one want to see the truth - the Angry Earth is FAR more dangerous in the long run.</string>
	<string key="1413_03_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Watcher Lin - Edengrove" name="WatcherLin" VO_Status="Not Recorded">Even with the creature diminished, we must be vigilant with these botanical fiends.\n\nMark my words - as soon as the Corruption is truly subdued, the Angry Earth will emerge as the greates threat we've ever known.</string>
	<string key="1414_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Watcher Reynolds - Edengrove" name="WatcherReynolds" gender="M" VO="1414_01_INIT_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Don't tell the other Wardens, but I think we've been getting a little Blight in our rations.\n\nI just hope it doesn't make us all sick.</string>
	<string key="1414_02_DefaultDialogue" speaker="Watcher Reynolds - Edengrove" name="WatcherReynolds" gender="M" VO_Status="Not Recorded">You there! I have need of someone light of foot. I have an urgent message bound for Reekwater to the South.</string>
	<string key="1415_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Watcher Minamide - Edengrove" name="WatcherMinamide" VO="1415_01_INIT_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Sometimes at night, the forest will suddenly get so quiet that it's almost impossible to sleep.\n\nI like some kind of background noise, you know.</string>
	<string key="1417_01_DefaultDialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Warden DeLeo - Edengrove" name="WardenDeLeo" VO="1417_01_INIT_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">I joined the Soulwardens to battle Corruption, not dither about in some forest.\n\nSo far, I've killed more mosquitos than Corrupted.</string>
	<string key="1422_00_Innkeep" speaker="Innkeep Yatim - Edengrove" name="InnkeepYatim" VO="1422_00_Innkeep_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Ah, you picked a wonderful time to visit! The leaves are so beautiful right now.\n\nPlease come in and make yourself comfortable.</string>
	<string key="1423_00_Innkeep" speaker="Innkeep Golding - Edengrove" name="InnkeepGolding" VO="1423_00_Innkeep_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Welcome to Archie's Boarding House. I'm the purveyor of this luxurious establishment.\n\nOur one and only room features four plush cots, some with "vintage" blankets. At least one of them has been laundered. Take your pick.</string>
	<string key="1424_01_DefaultDialogue" speaker="Master Fisher Davies - Edengrove" name="MasterFisherDavies" VO="1424_01_INIT_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Doo doo doo, I'm Master Fisher Davies…</string>
	<string key="1424_02_DefaultDialogue" speaker="Master Fisher Davies - Edengrove" name="MasterFisherDavies" VO="1424_02_INIT_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Ach, very well, very well. I guess this is supposed to prove a point that there's more to find in the water than just fish?</string>
	<string key="1424_03_DefaultDialogue" speaker="Master Fisher Davies - Edengrove" name="MasterFisherDavies" VO="1424_03_INIT_Default" VO_Status="Recorded">Thank you. Your help has been invaluable, friend. I'd say you're ready to catch most any fish in Aeternum.</string>
	<string key="1425_00_DefaultDialogue" speaker="Prospector Delgado - Edengrove" name="ProspectorDelgado" VO="1425_00_DefaultDialogue" VO_Status="Recorded">There's a place I know that might interest a glory-seeker like you.</string>
</resources>

