<resources xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy_Main">Craft recovery tinctures, powerful potions, and magical foci.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmith_Main">Craft melee weapons and shields.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineer_Main">Craft ranged weaponry, ammunition, and tools.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitter_Main">Craft hard and soft armors of all kinds.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioner_Main">Cook food and brew drinks that impart powerful, lasting effects.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillRepairing_Main">Reduces the durability lost when repairing an item. Reduces the resources required to repair an item.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging_Main">Gather more quickly, increase your chances of finding special resources, and unlock the ability to gather more powerful resources.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining_Main">Gather more quickly, increase your chances of finding special resources, and unlock the ability to gather more powerful resources.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting_Main">Gather more quickly and increase your chances of finding special resources.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning_Main">Gather more quickly and increase your chances of finding special resources.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping_Main">Improve your ability to survive on your own in the wild. Learn to build better camps and craft specialized items at them.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding_Main">Increase the amount of damage structures you build can sustain before collapsing.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillExploration_Main">COMING SOON™</string>
	<string key="TradeskillFishing_Main">COMING SOON™</string>
	<string key="TradeskillTracking_Main">COMING SOON™</string>
	<string key="TradeskillArmoring_Main">Craft hard and soft armors of all kinds.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillWeaponsmithing_Main">Craft melee weapons and shields.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCooking_Main">Cook food and brew drinks that impart powerful, lasting effects.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillJewelcrafting_Main">Craft Amulets, Rings, and Earrings that improve attributes and offer additional protection.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillArcana_main">Craft recovery tinctures, powerful potions, and magical foci.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillFurnishing_Main">Craft furniture, trophies, and house decorations.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillFSmelting_Main">Smelt raw ores into ingots so they can be used in crafting.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillWoodworking_Main">Cut wood into planks to they can be used in crafting.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLeatherworking_Main">Tan rawhide into leather so it can be used in crafting.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillWeaving_Main">Weave fibers into cloth so it can be used in crafting</string>
	<string key="TradeskillStonecutting_Main">Cut stone into bricks for building. Skilled stonecutters can also cut Gemstones.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy1_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Weak Potions that have regenerative properties at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy2_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Weak Coatings that imbue your weapon with various elements at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy3_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Weak Tinctures that cure Afflictions at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy5_Description">FINE CONCOCTIONS: Your potential as an Alchemist grows. You now have a chance to craft FINE Alchemical Concoctions. Fine Concoctions have more uses than their normal counterparts.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy6_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Distilled Tinctures that have restorative properties at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy7_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Distilled Potions that have various properties at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy8_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Distilled Coatings that imbue your weapon with various elements at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy9_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Distilled Tinctures that cure Afflictions at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy10_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Distilled Coatings that imbue your weapon with various afflictions at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy12_Description">SUPERIOR CONCOCTIONS: Your potential as an Alchemist grows. You now have a chance to craft SUPERIOR Alchemical Concoctions. Superior Concoctions have more uses than their normal counterparts.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy13_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Concentrated Tinctures that have restorative properties at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy14_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Concentrated Potions that have various properties at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy15_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Concentrated Coatings that imbue your weapon with various elements at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy16_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Concentrated Tinctures that cure Afflictions at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy17_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Concentrated Coatings that imbue your weapon with various afflictions at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy19_Description">ARTISAN CONCOCTIONS: Your potential as an Alchemist grows. You now have a chance to craft ARTISAN Alchemical Concoctions. Artisan Concoctions have more uses than their normal counterparts.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy20_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Strong Tinctures that have restorative properties at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy21_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Strong Potions that have various properties at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy22_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Strong Tinctures that cure Afflictions at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy23_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Strong Coatings that imbue your weapon with various elements or afflictions at an Alchemy Lab.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy25_Description">FLAWLESS CONCOCTIONS: Your potential as an Alchemist grows. You now have a chance to craft FLAWLESS Alchemical Concoctions. Flawless Concoctions have more uses than their normal counterparts.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing1_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Iron One-handed Weapons and Shields at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing2_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Iron Soldiers Armor at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing3_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Iron Tools at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing4_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Iron Two-handed Weapons at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing5_Description">FINE CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as a Blacksmith increases. You now have a chance to forge items of FINE QUALITY at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing6_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Steel One-handed Weapons at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing7_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Steel Soldiers Armor at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing8_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Steel Tools at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing9_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Steel Two-handed Weapons at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing10_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Steel Shields at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing11_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Steel Heavy Armor at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing12_Description">SUPERIOR CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as a Blacksmith increases. You now have a chance to forge items of SUPERIOR QUALITY at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing13_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Starmetal One-handed Weapons at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing14_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Starmetal Soldiers Armor at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing15_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Starmetal Tools at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing16_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Starmetal Two-handed Weapons at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing17_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Starmetal Shields at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing18_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Starmetal Heavy and Pathfinder Armor at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing19_Description">ARTISAN CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as a Blacksmith increases. You now have a chance to forge items of ARTISAN QUALITY at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing20_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Orichalcum One-handed Weapons and Shields at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing21_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Orichalcum Soldier and Inquisitor Armor at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing22_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Orichalcum Tools at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing23_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Orichalcum Two-handed Weapons at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing24_Description">You gain the knowledge to forge Orichalcum Heavy and Pathfinder Armor at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing25_Description">FLAWLESS CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as a Blacksmith increases. You now have a chance to forge items of FLAWLESS QUALITY at a Blacksmith.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping1_Description">LEAN-TO: Upgrades your camp to a LEAN-TO. Further increases your Health Regeneration when resting at your camp. The respawn cooldown at your Camp is reduced.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping2_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Iron Spears at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping3_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Rawhide Trapper Armor at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping4_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Antidote Drops at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping5_Description">FINE CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your Wilderness Survival potential increases. You now have a chance to craft items of FINE QUALITY at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping6_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Iron Arrows and Blessed Coating at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping7_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Healing Drops at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping8_Description">HALF TENT: Upgrades your camp to a HALF TENT. Further increases your Health Regeneration when resting at your camp. The respawn cooldown at your Camp is reduced.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping9_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Horn Bows at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping10_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Braised Vegetables, Barley Brew and Wellness Drops at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping11_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Blaze Coating at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping12_Description">SUPERIOR CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your Wilderness Survival potential increases. You now have a chance to craft items of SUPERIOR QUALITY at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping13_Description">SMALL TENT: Upgrades your camp to a SMALL TENT. Further increases your Health Regeneration when resting at your camp. The respawn cooldown at your Camp is reduced.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping14_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Fur Trapper Armor at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping15_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Starmetal Spears at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping16_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Composite Bows at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping17_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Meat and Braised Vegetables, Savory Brew and Warming Drops at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping18_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Starmetal Arrows at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping19_Description">ARTISAN CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your Wilderness Survival potential increases. You now have a chance to craft items of ARTISAN QUALITY at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping20_Description">LARGE TENT: Upgrades your camp to a LARGE TENT. Further increases your Health Regeneration when resting at your camp. The respawn cooldown at your Camp is reduced.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping21_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Orichalcum Spears at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping22_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Heavy Fur Trapper Armor at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping23_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Orichalcum Arrows and Purifying Drops at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping24_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Venom Coating at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping25_Description">FLAWLESS CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your Wilderness Survival potential increases. You now have a chance to craft items of FLAWLESS QUALITY at your Camp.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering1_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Treated Wood Bows at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering2_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Iron Siege Hammers at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering3_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Gunpowder at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering4_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Iron Arrows and Cartridges at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering5_Description">FINE CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as an Engineer increases. You now have a chance to craft items of FINE QUALITY at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering6_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Lacquered Wood Bows at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering7_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Steel Siege Hammers at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering8_Description">You have improved your chance to craft items of FINE QUALITY at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering9_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Steel Arrows and Cartridges at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering10_Description">You have improved your chance to craft items of FINE QUALITY at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering11_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Steel Muskets at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering12_Description">SUPERIOR CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as an Engineer increases. You now have a chance to craft items of SUPERIOR QUALITY at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering13_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Powder Kegs at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering14_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Wyrdwood Bows at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering15_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Starmetal Siege Hammers at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering16_Description">You have improved your chance to craft items of SUPERIOR QUALITY at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering17_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Starmetal Arrows and Cartridges at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering18_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Starmetal Muskets at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering19_Description">ARTISAN CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as an Engineer increases. You now have a chance to craft items of ARTISAN QUALITY at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering20_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Ironwood Bows at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering21_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Orichalcum Siege Hammers at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering22_Description">You have improved your chance to craft items of ARTISAN QUALITY at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering23_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Orichalcum Arrows and Cartridges at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering24_Description">You gain the knowledge to craft Orichalcum Muskets at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering25_Description">FLAWLESS CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as an Engineer increases. You now have a chance to craft items of FLAWLESS QUALITY at a Workshop.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting1_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Linen Duelists Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting2_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Coarse Leather Explorers Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting3_Description">You gain the knowledge to whitesmith Silver Trinkets at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting4_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Coarse Leather Adventurer's Satchel and Porter's Duffel at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting5_Description">FINE CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as an Outfitter increases. You now have a chance to craft items of FINE QUALITY at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting6_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Sateen Duelists Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting7_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Rugged Leather Explorers Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting8_Description">You have improved your chance to craft items of FINE QUALITY at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting9_Description">You gain the knowledge to whitesmith Gold Trinkets at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting10_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Rugged Leather Adventurer's Satchel and Porter's Duffel at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting11_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Sateen Sage Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting12_Description">SUPERIOR CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as an Outfitter increases. You now have a chance to craft items of SUPERIOR QUALITY at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting13_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Silk Duelists Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting14_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Layered Leather Explorers Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting15_Description">You gain the knowledge to whitesmith Platinum Trinkets at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting16_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Layered Leather Adventurer's Satchel and Porter's Duffel at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting17_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Silk Sage and Officers Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting18_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Layered Leather Witch Hunter's Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting19_Description">ARTISAN CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as an Outfitter increases. You now have a chance to craft items of ARTISAN QUALITY at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting20_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Infused Silk Duelists Armor and Infused Silk Courtiers Clothing at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting21_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Infused Leather Explorers Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting22_Description">You gain the knowledge to whitesmith Orichalcum Trinkets and to sew Infused Leather Adventurer's Satchel and Porter's Duffel at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting23_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Infused Silk Sage and Officers Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting24_Description">You gain the knowledge to sew Layered Leather Witch Hunter's and Plague Doctors Armor at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting25_Description">Flawless CRAFTSMANSHIP: Your potential as an Outfitter increases. You now have a chance to craft items of Flawless QUALITY at an Outfitter.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning1_Description">You learn basic recipes for Braises, Aqua Vitae and Brews which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning2_Description">You learn basic recipes for Cakes, Soups, Pies and Stews which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning3_Description">WASTE NOT: Your potential as a Cook increases. You now have a chance to craft 1 ADDITIONAL MEAL OR BREW at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning4_Description">You learn basic recipes for Fricassees, Porridge, Kickshaws and Pottage which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning5_Description">You learn basic recipes for Tonics, Infusions, Juices and Teas which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning6_Description">You have improved your chance to craft 1 ADDITIONAL MEAL OR BREW at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning7_Description">You learn advanced recipes for Braises, Aqua Vitae and Brews which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning8_Description">You learn advanced recipes for Cakes, Soups, Pies and Stews which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning9_Description">You have improved your chance to craft 1 ADDITIONAL MEAL OR BREW at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning10_Description">You learn advanced recipes for Kickshaws which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning11_Description">You learn advanced recipes for Fricassees, Porridge and Pottage which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning12_Description">WANT NOT: Your potential as a Cook increases. You now have a chance to craft 2 ADDITIONAL MEALS OR BREWS at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning13_Description">You learn advanced recipes for Tonics, Infusions, Juices and Teas which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning14_Description">You learn artisan recipes for Braises, Aqua Vitae and Brews which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning15_Description">You have improved your chance to craft 2 ADDITIONAL MEAL OR BREW at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning16_Description">You learn artisan recipes for Cakes, Soups, Pies and Stews which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning17_Description">You learn artisan recipes for Kickshaws which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning18_Description">You have improved your chance to craft 2 ADDITIONAL MEAL OR BREW at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning19_Description">You learn artisan recipes for Fricassees, Porridge and Pottage which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning20_Description">You learn artisan recipes for Tonics, Infusions, Juices and Teas which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning21_Description">WELL FED: Your potential as a Cook increases. You now have a small chance to craft 3 ADDITIONAL MEALS OR BREWS at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning22_Description">You learn how to craft Delightful Feasts which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning23_Description">You learn how to craft Confectionary Feasts which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning24_Description">You have improved your chance to craft 3 ADDITIONAL MEAL OR BREW at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning25_Description">You learn how to craft Hearty Feasts which are crafted at a Kitchen.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging1_Description">RUDIMENTARY CARPENTRY: You gain the knowledge to refine Timber. Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. You now gather slightly more wood from trees.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging2_Description">Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. You now gather slightly more wood from trees.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging3_Description">CONVENTIONAL CARPENTRY: You gain the knowledge to refine Lumber. Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. You now gather slightly more wood from trees.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging4_Description">Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now chop trees down slighty faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging5_Description">APPRENTICE LUMBERJACK: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Wood from UNCOMMON WOOD. You have a small chance to find UNCOMMON WOOD when you gather it. When refining wood, you waste less, resulting in bonus wood being refined.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging6_Description">Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. You now gather slightly more wood from trees.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging7_Description">COMPLEX CARPENTRY: You gain the knowledge to refine Wyrdwood Planks. Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now chop trees down slighty faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging8_Description">Your knowledge of woodlands increase, enabling you to detect when Wyrdwood Trees are nearby. Wyrdwood Trees now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging9_Description">Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. You now gather slightly more wood from trees.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging10_Description">INTRICATE CARPENTRY: You gain the knowledge to refine Ironwood Planks. Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now chop trees down slighty faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging11_Description">Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. You now gather more wood from trees.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging12_Description">JOURNEYMAN LUMBERJACK: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Wood from RARE WOOD.  You have a small chance to find RARE WOOD when you gather it. When refining wood, you waste less, resulting in bonus wood being refined.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging13_Description">Your knowledge of woodlands further increase, enabling you to detect when Ironwood Trees are nearby. Ironwood Trees now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging14_Description">Your skill as a Lumberjack increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now chop trees down slighty faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging15_Description">MASTER LUMBERJACK: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday wood from EXQUISITE WOOD. You have a small chance to find EXQUISITE WOOD when you gather it.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining1_Description">RUDIMENTARY SMELTING AND STONECUTTING: You gain the knowledge to refine Iron Ore, Silver Ore, and Stone Blocks. You can now sense Iron Veins. Iron Veins now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining2_Description">You can sense nearby Silver Veins. Silver Veins now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining3_Description">CONVENTIONAL SMELTING AND STONECUTTING: You gain the knowledge to refine Steel Ore, Gold Ore, and Stone Bricks. Your skill as a Miner increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you mine. You now mine more Ore and Stone from boulders.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining4_Description">You can sense nearby Seeping Stones. Seeping Stones now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining5_Description">APPRENTICE MINING: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Ore from UNCOMMON ORE. You have a small chance to find UNCOMMON ORE when you gather it. When refining Stone and Ore, you waste less, resulting in bonus Stone and Ore being refined. You now have a chance to discover Gemstone Shards when refining Silver Ore.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining6_Description">You can sense nearby Gold Veins. Gold Veins now appear on your compass. Your skill as a Miner increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you mine. You now mine slightly more Ore and Stone from boulders.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining7_Description">COMPLEX SMELTING AND STONECUTTING: You gain the knowledge to refine Starmetal Ore, Platinum Ore, and Lodestone Bricks. Your skill as a Miner increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now mine ore and stone faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining8_Description">You can sense nearby Starmetal. Starmetal appears on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining9_Description">You can sense nearby Lodestone. Lodestone now appears on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining10_Description">INTRICATE SMELTING AND STONECUTTING: You gain the knowledge to refine Orichalcum Ore and Infused Lodestone Bricks. Your skill as a Miner increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you mine. You now mine considerably more Ore and Stone from boulders.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining11_Description">You can now sense nearby Platinum Veins. Platinum Veins now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining12_Description">JOURNEYMAN MINING: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Ore from RARE ORE. You now have a small chance to find RARE ORE when you gather it. When refining Stone and Ore, you waste less, resulting in bonus Stone and Ore being refined. You now have a chance to discover Gemstone Fragments when refining Gold Ore.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining13_Description">You can now sense nearby Orichalcum Veins. Orichalcum Veins now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining14_Description">Your skill as a Miner increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now mine ore and stone faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining15_Description">MASTER MINING: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Ore from EXQUISITE ORE. You now have a small chance to find EXQUISITE ORE when you gather it. When refining Stone and Ore, you waste less, resulting in bonus Stone and Ore being refined. You now have a chance to discover Gemstones when refining Platinum Ore.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning1_Description">RUDIMENTARY TANNING: You gain the knowledge to refine Coarse Leather. You have learned the ability to track nearby small prey animals, such as Turkeys.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning2_Description">You have learned the ability to track nearby medium prey animals, such as Boars.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning3_Description">CONVENTIONAL TANNING: You gain the knowledge to refine Rugged Leather. Your skill at Skinning increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you field dress. You now gather more resources when skinning animal carcasses.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning4_Description">Your skill at Skinning increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now skin animal carcasses slightly faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning5_Description">APPRENTICE SKINNING: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Hide from UNCOMMON HIDE. You have a small chance to find UNCOMMON HIDE when you gather it. When refining Leather, you waste less, resulting in bonus Leather being refined.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning6_Description">You have learned the ability to track nearby large prey animals, such as Elk. Your skill at Skinning increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you field dress. You now gather slightly more resources when skinning animal carcasses.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning7_Description">COMPLEX TANNING: You gain the knowledge to refine Layered Leather. Your skill at Skinning increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now skin animal carcasses slightly faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning8_Description">You have learned the ability to track nearby small predators, such as Wolves.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning9_Description">Your skill at Skinning increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you field dress. You now gather more resources when skinning animal carcasses.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning10_Description">INTRICATE TANNING: You gain the knowledge to refine Infused Leather. Your skill at Skinning increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now skin animal carcasses slightly faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning11_Description">Your skill at Skinning increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you field dress. You now gather more resources when skinning animal carcasses.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning12_Description">JOURNEYMAN SKINNING: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Hide from RARE HIDE. You now have a small chance to find RARE HIDE when you gather it. When refining Leather, you waste less, resulting in bonus Leather being refined.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning13_Description">You have learned the ability to track nearby large predators, such as Bears.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning14_Description">Your skill at Skinning increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. You now skin animal carcasses slightly faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning15_Description">MASTER SKINNING: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Hide from EXQUISITE HIDE. You now have a small chance to find EXQUISITE HIDE when you gather it. When refining Cloth, you waste less, resulting in bonus Cloth being refined.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting1_Description">RUDIMENTARY WEAVING: You gain the knowledge to refine Linen. You have developed a sixth sense for edible plants, enabling you to detect nearby harvestable food.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting2_Description">Your sense of smell improves significantly, enabling you to detect ALCHEMY PLANTS from some distance away. ALCHEMY PLANTS will now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting3_Description">CONVENTIONAL WEAVING: You gain the knowledge to refine Sateen. Your skill as a Harvester increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. When using a sickle, you now gather more resources from plants.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting4_Description">Your skill as a Harvester increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. When using a sickle, you now gather plants slightly faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting5_Description">APPRENTICE HARVESTER: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Fibers from UNCOMMON FIBERS. You have a small chance to find UNCOMMON FIBERS when you gather them. When refining Cloth, you waste less, resulting in bonus Cloth being refined.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting6_Description">You gain the knowledge to refine Silk. Your eyes grow more keen, enabling you to detect ALCHEMY STONES from some distance away. ALCHEMY STONES will now appear on your compass. Your skill as a Harvester increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. When using a sickle, you now gather slightly more resources from plants.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting7_Description">COMPLEX WEAVING: You gain the knowledge to refine Silk. Your skill as a Harvester increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. When using a sickle, you now gather plants slightly faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting8_Description">Your ears grow more sensitive, enabling you to detect ALCHEMY CREATURES from some distance away. ALCHEMY CREATURES will now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting9_Description">Your skill as a Harvester increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. When using a sickle, you now gather more resources from plants.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting10_Description">INTRICATE WEAVING: You gain the knowledge to refine Infused Silk. Your skill as a Harvester increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. When using a sickle, you now gather plants slightly faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting11_Description">Your skill as a Harvester increases, as does your ability to make the most of what you gather. When using a sickle, you now gather more resources from plants.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting12_Description">JOURNEYMAN HARVESTER: You have begun to learn to discern normal, everyday Fibers from RARE FIBERS. You have small chance to find RARE FIBERS when you gather them. When refining Cloth, you waste less, resulting in bonus Cloth being refined.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting13_Description">Your knowledge of New World Hemp has grown to the point of you being able to detect it when it is nearby. Hemp Plants now appear on your compass.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting14_Description">Your skill as a Harvester increases, as does your ability to utilize the tools of your trade. When using a sickle, you now gather plants slightly faster.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting15_Description">MASTER HARVESTER: You have begun to learn to discern normal, every day Fibers from EXQUISITE FIBERS. You have a small chance to find EXQUISITE FIBERS when you gather them. When refining Cloth, you waste less, resulting in bonus Cloth being refined.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing1_Description">Reduces the RESOURCES REQUIRED TO REPAIR items by 5%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing2_Description">Reduces LOSS TO MAXIMUM DURABILITY when repairing an item by 10%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing3_Description">Reduces the RESOURCES REQUIRED TO REPAIR items by 8%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing4_Description">Reduces the RESOURCES REQUIRED TO REPAIR items by 10%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing5_Description">Reduces LOSS TO MAXIMUM DURABILITY when repairing an item by an additional 15%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing6_Description">Reduces the RESOURCES REQUIRED TO REPAIR items by an additional 10%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing7_Description">Reduces the RESOURCES REQUIRED TO REPAIR items by an additional 12%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing8_Description">Reduces LOSS TO MAXIMUM DURABILITY when repairing an item by an additional 25%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing9_Description">Reduces the RESOURCES REQUIRED TO REPAIR items by an additional 15%.</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing10_Description">Reduces LOSS TO MAXIMUM DURABILITY when repairing an item by an additional 30%.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding1_Description">APPRENTICE ARCHITECT: Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now significantly sturdier and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding2_Description">Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now slightly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding3_Description">Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now slightly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding4_Description">Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now slightly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding5_Description">JOURNEYMAN ARCHICTECT: Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now significantly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding6_Description">Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now slightly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding7_Description">Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now slightly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding8_Description">Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now slightly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding9_Description">Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now slightly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding10_Description">MASTER ARCHITECT: Your skill as a builder grows. Structures that you build are now significantly sturdier than before and can sustain more damage before falling. Only new structures are affected.</string>
	<string key="ui_onehanded_weapons">One-Handed Weapons</string>
	<string key="ui_twohanded_weapons">Two-Handed Weapons</string>
	<string key="ui_ranged_weapons">Ranged Weapons</string>
	<string key="ui_magic_skills">Magic Skills</string>
	<string key="ui_weaponmastery_description">Weapon skills are advanced by using weapons of that type. Each level grants a point to spend to unlock upgrades specific to that weapon.</string>
	<string key="ui_weaponmastery_in_progress" comment="this is a temporary message to explain the limited number of weapon mastery trees available">Weapon Mastery trees are still in development. More weapons coming soon.</string>
	<string key="ui_farmplants">Farm Plants</string>
	<string key="ui_hemp">Hemp</string>
	<string key="ui_hempt4">Silkweed</string>
	<string key="ui_hempt5">Wirefiber</string>
	<string key="ui_alchemy1">Magical Plants</string>
	<string key="ui_alchemy2">Magical Stones</string>
	<string key="ui_alchemy3">Magical Creatures</string>
	<string key="iconTypeUnlock_Pigment">Fungi</string>
	<string key="ui_smallprey">Small Prey</string>
	<string key="ui_mediumprey">Medium Prey</string>
	<string key="ui_largeprey">Large Prey</string>
	<string key="ui_smallpredator">Small Predator</string>
	<string key="ui_largepredator">Large Predator</string>
	<string key="ui_iron">Iron</string>
	<string key="ui_oil">Oil</string>
	<string key="ui_silver">Silver</string>
	<string key="ui_lodestone">Lodestone</string>
	<string key="ui_gold">Gold</string>
	<string key="ui_starmetal">Starmetal</string>
	<string key="ui_platinum">Platinum</string>
	<string key="ui_orichalcum">Orichalcum</string>
	<string key="ui_wyrdwood">Wyrdwood</string>
	<string key="ui_ironwood">Ironwood</string>
	<string key="ui_toolrequired">Tool Required</string>
	<string key="ui_alchemyStones">Alchemy Stones</string>
	<string key="ui_skinningOnly">Skinning</string>
	<string key="ui_trackingOnly">Tracking</string>
	<string key="ui_canSkinLevel">You can skin animals that are up to &lt;font color={levelColor}&gt;level {maxGatherLevel}&lt;/font&gt;</string>
	<string key="ui_skillToSkinLevel">At skill level {skillLevel} you will be able to skin animals up to level {maxGatherLevel}</string>
	<string key="ui_skillToSkinLevelShort">Skill level: {skillLevel} - Animal level: {maxGatherLevel}</string>
	<string key="iconTypeUnlock_youngtrees">Young Trees</string>
	<string key="iconTypeUnlock_maturetrees">Mature Trees</string>
</resources>

