<resources>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy_Main">[[Čřäft hëäłïňğ tïňčtüřëš, pöwëřfüł pötïöňš, dëädłŷ wëäpöň čöätïňğš, äňd mäğïčäł čäštïňğ ğäüňtłëtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmith_Main">[[Čřäft mëłëë wëäpöňš äňd mëtäł äřmöřš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineer_Main">[[Čřäft řäňğëd äňd šïëğë wëäpöňřŷ.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitter_Main">[[Čřäft třïňkëtš äňd łïğht äřmöřš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioner_Main">[[Čöök fööd äňd břëw dřïňkš thät ïmpäřt pöwëřfüł, łäštïňğ ëffëčtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillRepairing_Main">[[Řëdüčëš thë düřäbïłïtŷ łöšt whëň řëpäïřïňğ äň ïtëm. Řëdüčëš thë řëšöüřčëš řëqüïřëd tö řëpäïř äň ïtëm.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging_Main">[[Ïmpřövë ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ğäthëř třëëš fäštëř, ïň hïğhëř qüäňtïtïëš, äňd ät hïğhëř řäřïtïëš. Ïňčřëäšë ŷöüř čhäňčëš öf ğëttïňğ ëxtřä wööd whëň řëfïňïňğ.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining_Main">[[Ïmpřövë ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ğäthëř böüłdëřš äňd vëïňš fäštëř, ïň hïğhëř qüäňtïtïëš, äňd ät hïğhëř řäřïtïëš. Ïňčřëäšë ŷöüř čhäňčëš öf ğëttïňğ ëxtřä štöňë äňd mëtäł whëň řëfïňïňğ.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting_Main">[[Ïmpřövë ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ğäthëř häřvëštäbłë płäňtš fäštëř, ïň hïğhëř qüäňtïtïëš, äňd ät hïğhëř řäřïtïëš. Ïňčřëäšë ŷöüř čhäňčëš öf ğëttïňğ ëxtřä čłöth whëň řëfïňïňğ.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning_Main">[[Ïmpřövë ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ğäthëř hïdëš fäštëř, ïň hïğhëř qüäňtïtïëš, äňd ät hïğhëř řäřïtïëš. Ïňčřëäšë ŷöüř čhäňčëš öf ğëttïňğ ëxtřä łëäthëř whëň řëfïňïňğ.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping_Main">[[Ïmpřövë ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö šüřvïvë ïň öň ŷöüř öwň ïň thë wïłd. Łëäřň tö büïłd bëttëř čämpš äňd čřäft špëčïäłïžëd ïtëmš ät thëm.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding_Main">[[Ïňčřëäšë thë ämöüňt öf dämäğë štřüčtüřëš ŷöü büïłd čäň šüštäïň bëföřë čöłłäpšïňğ.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillExploration_Main">[[ČÖMÏŇĞ ŠÖÖŇ™]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillFishing_Main">[[ČÖMÏŇĞ ŠÖÖŇ™]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillTracking_Main">[[ČÖMÏŇĞ ŠÖÖŇ™]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy1_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Wëäk Pötïöňš thät hävë řëğëňëřätïvë přöpëřtïëš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy2_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Wëäk Čöätïňğš thät ïmbüë ŷöüř wëäpöň wïth väřïöüš ëłëmëňtš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy3_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Wëäk Tïňčtüřëš thät čüřë Äffłïčtïöňš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy4_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Ïřöň Čëłëštïäł Hëäłïňğ Ğäüňtłëtš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy5_Description">[[FÏŇË ČÖŇČÖČTÏÖŇŠ: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Äłčhëmïšt ğřöwš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft FÏŇË Äłčhëmïčäł Čöňčöčtïöňš. Fïňë Čöňčöčtïöňš hävë möřë üšëš thäň thëïř ňöřmäł čöüňtëřpäřtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy6_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Dïštïłłëd Tïňčtüřëš thät hävë řëštöřätïvë přöpëřtïëš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy7_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Dïštïłłëd Pötïöňš thät hävë väřïöüš přöpëřtïëš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy8_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Dïštïłłëd Čöätïňğš thät ïmbüë ŷöüř wëäpöň wïth väřïöüš ëłëmëňtš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy9_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Dïštïłłëd Tïňčtüřëš thät čüřë Äffłïčtïöňš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy10_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Dïštïłłëd Čöätïňğš thät ïmbüë ŷöüř wëäpöň wïth väřïöüš äffłïčtïöňš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy11_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štëëł Čëłëštïäł Hëäłïňğ Ğäüňtłëtš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy12_Description">[[ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ ČÖŇČÖČTÏÖŇŠ: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Äłčhëmïšt ğřöwš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ Äłčhëmïčäł Čöňčöčtïöňš. Šüpëřïöř Čöňčöčtïöňš hävë möřë üšëš thäň thëïř ňöřmäł čöüňtëřpäřtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy13_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Čöňčëňtřätëd Tïňčtüřëš thät hävë řëštöřätïvë přöpëřtïëš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy14_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Čöňčëňtřätëd Pötïöňš thät hävë väřïöüš přöpëřtïëš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy15_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Čöňčëňtřätëd Čöätïňğš thät ïmbüë ŷöüř wëäpöň wïth väřïöüš ëłëmëňtš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy16_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Čöňčëňtřätëd Tïňčtüřëš thät čüřë Äffłïčtïöňš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy17_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Čöňčëňtřätëd Čöätïňğš thät ïmbüë ŷöüř wëäpöň wïth väřïöüš äffłïčtïöňš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy18_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štäřmëtäł Čëłëštïäł Hëäłïňğ Ğäüňtłëtš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy19_Description">[[ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ ČÖŇČÖČTÏÖŇŠ: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Äłčhëmïšt ğřöwš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ Äłčhëmïčäł Čöňčöčtïöňš. Äřtïšäň Čöňčöčtïöňš hävë möřë üšëš thäň thëïř ňöřmäł čöüňtëřpäřtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy20_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štřöňğ Tïňčtüřëš thät hävë řëštöřätïvë přöpëřtïëš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy21_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štřöňğ Pötïöňš thät hävë väřïöüš přöpëřtïëš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy22_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štřöňğ Tïňčtüřëš thät čüřë Äffłïčtïöňš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy23_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štřöňğ Čöätïňğš thät ïmbüë ŷöüř wëäpöň wïth väřïöüš ëłëmëňtš öř äffłïčtïöňš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy24_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Öřïčhäłčüm Čëłëštïäł Hëäłïňğ Ğäüňtłëtš ät äň Äłčhëmŷ Łäb.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillAlchemy25_Description">[[FŁÄWŁËŠŠ ČÖŇČÖČTÏÖŇŠ: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Äłčhëmïšt ğřöwš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft FŁÄWŁËŠŠ Äłčhëmïčäł Čöňčöčtïöňš. Fłäwłëšš Čöňčöčtïöňš hävë möřë üšëš thäň thëïř ňöřmäł čöüňtëřpäřtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing1_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Ïřöň Öňë-häňdëd Wëäpöňš äňd Šhïëłdš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing2_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Ïřöň Šöłdïëřš Äřmöř ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing3_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Ïřöň Tööłš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing4_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Ïřöň Twö-häňdëd Wëäpöňš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing5_Description">[[FÏŇË ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš ä Błäčkšmïth ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö föřğë ïtëmš öf FÏŇË QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing6_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štëëł Öňë-häňdëd Wëäpöňš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing7_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štëëł Šöłdïëřš Äřmöř ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing8_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štëëł Tööłš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing9_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štëëł Twö-häňdëd Wëäpöňš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing10_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štëëł Šhïëłdš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing11_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štëëł Hëävŷ Äřmöř ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing12_Description">[[ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš ä Błäčkšmïth ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö föřğë ïtëmš öf ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing13_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štäřmëtäł Öňë-häňdëd Wëäpöňš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing14_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štäřmëtäł Šöłdïëřš Äřmöř ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing15_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štäřmëtäł Tööłš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing16_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štäřmëtäł Twö-häňdëd Wëäpöňš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing17_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štäřmëtäł Šhïëłdš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing18_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Štäřmëtäł Hëävŷ äňd Päthfïňdëř Äřmöř ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing19_Description">[[ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš ä Błäčkšmïth ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö föřğë ïtëmš öf ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing20_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Öřïčhäłčüm Öňë-häňdëd Wëäpöňš äňd Šhïëłdš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing21_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Öřïčhäłčüm Šöłdïëř äňd Ïňqüïšïtöř Äřmöř ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing22_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Öřïčhäłčüm Tööłš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing23_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Öřïčhäłčüm Twö-häňdëd Wëäpöňš ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing24_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö föřğë Öřïčhäłčüm Hëävŷ äňd Päthfïňdëř Äřmöř ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBlacksmithing25_Description">[[FŁÄWŁËŠŠ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš ä Błäčkšmïth ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö föřğë ïtëmš öf FŁÄWŁËŠŠ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät ä Błäčkšmïth.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping1_Description">[[ŁËÄŇ-TÖ: Üpğřädğëš ŷöüř čämp tö ä ŁËÄŇ-TÖ. Füřthëř ïňčřëäšëš ŷöüř Hëäłth Řëğëňëřätïöň whëň řëštïňğ ät ŷöüř čämp. Thë řëšpäwň čööłdöwň ät ŷöüř Čämp ïš řëdüčëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping2_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Ïřöň Špëäřš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping3_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Řäwhïdë Třäppëř Äřmöř ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping4_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Äňtïdötë Dřöpš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping5_Description">[[FÏŇË ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř Wïłdëřňëšš Šüřvïväł pötëňtïäł ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf FÏŇË QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping6_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Ïřöň Äřřöwš äňd Błëššëd Čöätïňğ ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping7_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Hëäłïňğ Dřöpš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping8_Description">[[HÄŁF TËŇT: Üpğřädğëš ŷöüř čämp tö ä HÄŁF TËŇT. Füřthëř ïňčřëäšëš ŷöüř Hëäłth Řëğëňëřätïöň whëň řëštïňğ ät ŷöüř čämp. Thë řëšpäwň čööłdöwň ät ŷöüř Čämp ïš řëdüčëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping9_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Höřň Böwš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping10_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Břäïšëd Vëğëtäbłëš, Bäřłëŷ Břëw äňd Wëłłňëšš Dřöpš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping11_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Błäžë Čöätïňğ ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping12_Description">[[ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř Wïłdëřňëšš Šüřvïväł pötëňtïäł ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping13_Description">[[ŠMÄŁŁ TËŇT: Üpğřädğëš ŷöüř čämp tö ä ŠMÄŁŁ TËŇT. Füřthëř ïňčřëäšëš ŷöüř Hëäłth Řëğëňëřätïöň whëň řëštïňğ ät ŷöüř čämp. Thë řëšpäwň čööłdöwň ät ŷöüř Čämp ïš řëdüčëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping14_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Füř Třäppëř Äřmöř ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping15_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štäřmëtäł Špëäřš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping16_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Čömpöšïtë Böwš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping17_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Mëät äňd Břäïšëd Vëğëtäbłëš, Šävöřŷ Břëw äňd Wäřmïňğ Dřöpš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping18_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štäřmëtäł Äřřöwš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping19_Description">[[ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř Wïłdëřňëšš Šüřvïväł pötëňtïäł ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping20_Description">[[ŁÄŘĞË TËŇT: Üpğřädğëš ŷöüř čämp tö ä ŁÄŘĞË TËŇT. Füřthëř ïňčřëäšëš ŷöüř Hëäłth Řëğëňëřätïöň whëň řëštïňğ ät ŷöüř čämp. Thë řëšpäwň čööłdöwň ät ŷöüř Čämp ïš řëdüčëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping21_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Öřïčhäłčüm Špëäřš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping22_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Hëävŷ Füř Třäppëř Äřmöř ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping23_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Öřïčhäłčüm Äřřöwš äňd Püřïfŷïňğ Dřöpš ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping24_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Vëňöm Čöätïňğ ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillCamping25_Description">[[FŁÄWŁËŠŠ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř Wïłdëřňëšš Šüřvïväł pötëňtïäł ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf FŁÄWŁËŠŠ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät ŷöüř Čämp.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering1_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Třëätëd Wööd Böwš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering2_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Ïřöň Šïëğë Hämmëřš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering3_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Ğüňpöwdëř ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering4_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Ïřöň Äřřöwš äňd Čäřtřïdğëš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering5_Description">[[FÏŇË ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Ëňğïňëëř ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf FÏŇË QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering6_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Łäčqüëřëd Wööd Böwš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering7_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štëëł Šïëğë Hämmëřš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering8_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf FÏŇË QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering9_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štëëł Äřřöwš äňd Čäřtřïdğëš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering10_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf FÏŇË QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering11_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štëëł Müškëtš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering12_Description">[[ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Ëňğïňëëř ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering13_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Pöwdëř Këğš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering14_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Wŷřdwööd Böwš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering15_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štäřmëtäł Šïëğë Hämmëřš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering16_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering17_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štäřmëtäł Äřřöwš äňd Čäřtřïdğëš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering18_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Štäřmëtäł Müškëtš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering19_Description">[[ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Ëňğïňëëř ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering20_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Ïřöňwööd Böwš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering21_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Öřïčhäłčüm Šïëğë Hämmëřš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering22_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering23_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Öřïčhäłčüm Äřřöwš äňd Čäřtřïdğëš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering24_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö čřäft Öřïčhäłčüm Müškëtš ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillEngineering25_Description">[[FŁÄWŁËŠŠ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Ëňğïňëëř ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf FŁÄWŁËŠŠ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Ëňğïňëëřïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting1_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Łïňëň Düëłïštš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting2_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Čöäřšë Łëäthëř Ëxpłöřëřš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting3_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö whïtëšmïth Šïłvëř Třïňkëtš ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting4_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Čöäřšë Łëäthëř Ädvëňtüřëř'š Šätčhëł äňd Pöřtëř'š Düffëł ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting5_Description">[[FÏŇË ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Öütfïttëř ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf FÏŇË QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Öütfïttëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting6_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Šätëëň Düëłïštš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting7_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Řüğğëd Łëäthëř Ëxpłöřëřš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting8_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf FÏŇË QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting9_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö whïtëšmïth Ğöłd Třïňkëtš ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting10_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Řüğğëd Łëäthëř Ädvëňtüřëř'š Šätčhëł äňd Pöřtëř'š Düffëł ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting11_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Šätëëň Šäğë Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting12_Description">[[ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Öütfïttëř ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf ŠÜPËŘÏÖŘ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Öütfïttëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting13_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Šïłk Düëłïštš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting14_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Łäŷëřëd Łëäthëř Ëxpłöřëřš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting15_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö whïtëšmïth Płätïňüm Třïňkëtš ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting16_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Łäŷëřëd Łëäthëř Ädvëňtüřëř'š Šätčhëł äňd Pöřtëř'š Düffëł ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting17_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Šïłk Šäğë äňd Öffïčëřš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting18_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Łäŷëřëd Łëäthëř Wïtčh Hüňtëř'š Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting19_Description">[[ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Öütfïttëř ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf ÄŘTÏŠÄŇ QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Öütfïttëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting20_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Ïňfüšëd Šïłk Düëłïštš Äřmöř äňd Ïňfüšëd Šïłk Čöüřtïëřš Čłöthïňğ ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting21_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Ïňfüšëd Łëäthëř Ëxpłöřëřš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting22_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö whïtëšmïth Öřïčhäłčüm Třïňkëtš äňd tö šëw Ïňfüšëd Łëäthëř Ädvëňtüřëř'š Šätčhëł äňd Pöřtëř'š Düffëł ät äň Öütfïttëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting23_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Ïňfüšëd Šïłk Šäğë äňd Öffïčëřš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting24_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö šëw Łäŷëřëd Łëäthëř Wïtčh Hüňtëř'š äňd Płäğüë Döčtöřš Äřmöř ät äň Öütfïttëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillOutfitting25_Description">[[Fłäwłëšš ČŘÄFTŠMÄŇŠHÏP: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš äň Öütfïttëř ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft ïtëmš öf Fłäwłëšš QÜÄŁÏTŶ ät äň Öütfïttëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning1_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň bäšïč řëčïpëš föř Břäïšëš, Äqüä Vïtäë äňd Břëwš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning2_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň bäšïč řëčïpëš föř Čäkëš, Šöüpš, Pïëš äňd Štëwš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning3_Description">[[WÄŠTË ŇÖT: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš ä Čöök ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft 1 ÄDDÏTÏÖŇÄŁ MËÄŁ ÖŘ BŘËW ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning4_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň bäšïč řëčïpëš föř Fřïčäššëëš, Pöřřïdğë, Kïčkšhäwš äňd Pöttäğë whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning5_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň bäšïč řëčïpëš föř Töňïčš, Ïňfüšïöňš, Jüïčëš äňd Tëäš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning6_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft 1 ÄDDÏTÏÖŇÄŁ MËÄŁ ÖŘ BŘËW ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning7_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň ädväňčëd řëčïpëš föř Břäïšëš, Äqüä Vïtäë äňd Břëwš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning8_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň ädväňčëd řëčïpëš föř Čäkëš, Šöüpš, Pïëš äňd Štëwš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning9_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft 1 ÄDDÏTÏÖŇÄŁ MËÄŁ ÖŘ BŘËW ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning10_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň ädväňčëd řëčïpëš föř Kïčkšhäwš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning11_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň ädväňčëd řëčïpëš föř Fřïčäššëëš, Pöřřïdğë äňd Pöttäğë whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning12_Description">[[WÄŇT ŇÖT: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš ä Čöök ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö čřäft 2 ÄDDÏTÏÖŇÄŁ MËÄŁŠ ÖŘ BŘËWŠ ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning13_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň ädväňčëd řëčïpëš föř Töňïčš, Ïňfüšïöňš, Jüïčëš äňd Tëäš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning14_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň äřtïšäň řëčïpëš föř Břäïšëš, Äqüä Vïtäë äňd Břëwš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning15_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft 2 ÄDDÏTÏÖŇÄŁ MËÄŁ ÖŘ BŘËW ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning16_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň äřtïšäň řëčïpëš föř Čäkëš, Šöüpš, Pïëš äňd Štëwš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning17_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň äřtïšäň řëčïpëš föř Kïčkšhäwš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning18_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft 2 ÄDDÏTÏÖŇÄŁ MËÄŁ ÖŘ BŘËW ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning19_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň äřtïšäň řëčïpëš föř Fřïčäššëëš, Pöřřïdğë äňd Pöttäğë whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning20_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň äřtïšäň řëčïpëš föř Töňïčš, Ïňfüšïöňš, Jüïčëš äňd Tëäš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning21_Description">[[WËŁŁ FËD: Ŷöüř pötëňtïäł äš ä Čöök ïňčřëäšëš. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö čřäft 3 ÄDDÏTÏÖŇÄŁ MËÄŁŠ ÖŘ BŘËWŠ ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning22_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň höw tö čřäft Dëłïğhtfüł Fëäštš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning23_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň höw tö čřäft Čöňfëčtïöňäřŷ Fëäštš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning24_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë ïmpřövëd ŷöüř čhäňčë tö čřäft 3 ÄDDÏTÏÖŇÄŁ MËÄŁ ÖŘ BŘËW ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillProvisioning25_Description">[[Ŷöü łëäřň höw tö čřäft Hëäřtŷ Fëäštš whïčh äřë čřäftëd ät ä Čöökïňğ Štätïöň.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging1_Description">[[ŘÜDÏMËŇTÄŘŶ ČÄŘPËŇTŘŶ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Tïmbëř. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř šłïğhtłŷ möřë wööd fřöm třëëš. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging2_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř šłïğhtłŷ möřë wööd fřöm třëëš. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging3_Description">[[ČÖŇVËŇTÏÖŇÄŁ ČÄŘPËŇTŘŶ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Łümbëř. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř šłïğhtłŷ möřë wööd fřöm třëëš. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging4_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw čhöp třëëš döwň šłïğhtŷ fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging5_Description">[[ÄPPŘËŇTÏČË ŁÜMBËŘJÄČK: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Wööd fřöm ÜŇČÖMMÖŇ WÖÖD. Ŷöü hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ÜŇČÖMMÖŇ WÖÖD whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït. Whëň řëfïňïňğ wööd, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš wööd bëïňğ řëfïňëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging6_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř šłïğhtłŷ möřë wööd fřöm třëëš. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging7_Description">[[ČÖMPŁËX ČÄŘPËŇTŘŶ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Wŷřdwööd Płäňkš. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw čhöp třëëš döwň šłïğhtŷ fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging8_Description">[[Ŷöüř kňöwłëdğë öf wöödłäňdš ïňčřëäšë, ëňäbłïňğ ŷöü tö dëtëčt whëň Wŷřdwööd Třëëš äřë ňëäřbŷ. Wŷřdwööd Třëëš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging9_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř šłïğhtłŷ möřë wööd fřöm třëëš. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging10_Description">[[ÏŇTŘÏČÄTË ČÄŘPËŇTŘŶ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Ïřöňwööd Płäňkš. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw čhöp třëëš döwň šłïğhtŷ fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging11_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř möřë wööd fřöm třëëš. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging12_Description">[[JÖÜŘŇËŶMÄŇ ŁÜMBËŘJÄČK: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Wööd fřöm ŘÄŘË WÖÖD.  Ŷöü hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ŘÄŘË WÖÖD whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït. Whëň řëfïňïňğ wööd, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš wööd bëïňğ řëfïňëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging13_Description">[[Ŷöüř kňöwłëdğë öf wöödłäňdš füřthëř ïňčřëäšë, ëňäbłïňğ ŷöü tö dëtëčt whëň Ïřöňwööd Třëëš äřë ňëäřbŷ. Ïřöňwööd Třëëš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging14_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Łümbëřjäčk ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw čhöp třëëš döwň šłïğhtŷ fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillLogging15_Description">[[MÄŠTËŘ ŁÜMBËŘJÄČK: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ wööd fřöm ËXQÜÏŠÏTË WÖÖD. Ŷöü hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ËXQÜÏŠÏTË WÖÖD whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining1_Description">[[ŘÜDÏMËŇTÄŘŶ ŠMËŁTÏŇĞ ÄŇD MÄŠÖŇŘŶ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Ïřöň Öřë, Šïłvëř Öřë, äňd Štöňë Błöčkš. Ŷöü čäň ňöw šëňšë Ïřöň Vëïňš. Ïřöň Vëïňš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining2_Description">[[Ŷöü čäň šëňšë ňëäřbŷ Šïłvëř Vëïňš. Šïłvëř Vëïňš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining3_Description">[[ČÖŇVËŇTÏÖŇÄŁ ŠMËŁTÏŇĞ ÄŇD MÄŠÖŇŘŶ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Štëëł Öřë, Ğöłd Öřë, äňd Štöňë Břïčkš. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Mïňëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü mïňë. Ŷöü ňöw mïňë möřë Öřë äňd Štöňë fřöm böüłdëřš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining4_Description">[[Ŷöü čäň šëňšë ňëäřbŷ Šëëpïňğ Štöňëš. Šëëpïňğ Štöňëš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining5_Description">[[ÄPPŘËŇTÏČË MÏŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Öřë fřöm ÜŇČÖMMÖŇ ÖŘË. Ŷöü hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ÜŇČÖMMÖŇ ÖŘË whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït. Whëň řëfïňïňğ Štöňë äňd Öřë, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš Štöňë äňd Öřë bëïňğ řëfïňëd. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö dïščövëř Ğëmštöňë Šhäřdš whëň řëfïňïňğ Šïłvëř Öřë.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining6_Description">[[Ŷöü čäň šëňšë ňëäřbŷ Ğöłd Vëïňš. Ğöłd Vëïňš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Mïňëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü mïňë. Ŷöü ňöw mïňë šłïğhtłŷ möřë Öřë äňd Štöňë fřöm böüłdëřš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining7_Description">[[ČÖMPŁËX ŠMËŁTÏŇĞ ÄŇD MÄŠÖŇŘŶ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Štäřmëtäł Öřë, Płätïňüm Öřë, äňd Łödëštöňë Břïčkš. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Mïňëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw mïňë öřë äňd štöňë fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining8_Description">[[Ŷöü čäň šëňšë ňëäřbŷ Štäřmëtäł. Štäřmëtäł äppëäřš öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining9_Description">[[Ŷöü čäň šëňšë ňëäřbŷ Łödëštöňë. Łödëštöňë ňöw äppëäřš öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining10_Description">[[ÏŇTŘÏČÄTË ŠMËŁTÏŇĞ ÄŇD MÄŠÖŇŘŶ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Öřïčhäłčüm Öřë äňd Ïňfüšëd Łödëštöňë Břïčkš. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Mïňëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü mïňë. Ŷöü ňöw mïňë čöňšïdëřäbłŷ möřë Öřë äňd Štöňë fřöm böüłdëřš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining11_Description">[[Ŷöü čäň ňöw šëňšë ňëäřbŷ Płätïňüm Vëïňš. Płätïňüm Vëïňš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining12_Description">[[JÖÜŘŇËŶMÄŇ MÏŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Öřë fřöm ŘÄŘË ÖŘË. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ŘÄŘË ÖŘË whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït. Whëň řëfïňïňğ Štöňë äňd Öřë, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš Štöňë äňd Öřë bëïňğ řëfïňëd. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö dïščövëř Ğëmštöňë Fřäğmëňtš whëň řëfïňïňğ Ğöłd Öřë.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining13_Description">[[Ŷöü čäň ňöw šëňšë ňëäřbŷ Öřïčhäłčüm Vëïňš. Öřïčhäłčüm Vëïňš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining14_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Mïňëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw mïňë öřë äňd štöňë fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillMining15_Description">[[MÄŠTËŘ MÏŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Öřë fřöm ËXQÜÏŠÏTË ÖŘË. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ËXQÜÏŠÏTË ÖŘË whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït. Whëň řëfïňïňğ Štöňë äňd Öřë, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš Štöňë äňd Öřë bëïňğ řëfïňëd. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä čhäňčë tö dïščövëř Ğëmštöňëš whëň řëfïňïňğ Płätïňüm Öřë.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning1_Description">[[ŘÜDÏMËŇTÄŘŶ TÄŇŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Čöäřšë Łëäthëř. Ŷöü hävë łëäřňëd thë äbïłïtŷ tö třäčk ňëäřbŷ šmäłł přëŷ äňïmäłš, šüčh äš Tüřkëŷš. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning2_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë łëäřňëd thë äbïłïtŷ tö třäčk ňëäřbŷ mëdïüm přëŷ äňïmäłš, šüčh äš Böäřš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning3_Description">[[ČÖŇVËŇTÏÖŇÄŁ TÄŇŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Řüğğëd Łëäthëř. Ŷöüř škïłł ät Škïňňïňğ ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü fïëłd dřëšš. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř möřë řëšöüřčëš whëň škïňňïňğ äňïmäł čäřčäššëš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning4_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł ät Škïňňïňğ ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw škïň äňïmäł čäřčäššëš šłïğhtłŷ fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning5_Description">[[ÄPPŘËŇTÏČË ŠKÏŇŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Hïdë fřöm ÜŇČÖMMÖŇ HÏDË. Ŷöü hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ÜŇČÖMMÖŇ HÏDË whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït. Whëň řëfïňïňğ Łëäthëř, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš Łëäthëř bëïňğ řëfïňëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning6_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë łëäřňëd thë äbïłïtŷ tö třäčk ňëäřbŷ łäřğë přëŷ äňïmäłš, šüčh äš Ëłk. Ŷöüř škïłł ät Škïňňïňğ ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü fïëłd dřëšš. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř šłïğhtłŷ möřë řëšöüřčëš whëň škïňňïňğ äňïmäł čäřčäššëš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning7_Description">[[ČÖMPŁËX TÄŇŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Łäŷëřëd Łëäthëř. Ŷöüř škïłł ät Škïňňïňğ ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw škïň äňïmäł čäřčäššëš šłïğhtłŷ fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning8_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë łëäřňëd thë äbïłïtŷ tö třäčk ňëäřbŷ šmäłł přëdätöřš, šüčh äš Wöłvëš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning9_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł ät Škïňňïňğ ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü fïëłd dřëšš. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř möřë řëšöüřčëš whëň škïňňïňğ äňïmäł čäřčäššëš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning10_Description">[[ÏŇTŘÏČÄTË TÄŇŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Ïňfüšëd Łëäthëř. Ŷöüř škïłł ät Škïňňïňğ ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw škïň äňïmäł čäřčäššëš šłïğhtłŷ fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning11_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł ät Škïňňïňğ ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü fïëłd dřëšš. Ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř möřë řëšöüřčëš whëň škïňňïňğ äňïmäł čäřčäššëš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning12_Description">[[JÖÜŘŇËŶMÄŇ ŠKÏŇŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Hïdë fřöm ŘÄŘË HÏDË. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ŘÄŘË HÏDË whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït. Whëň řëfïňïňğ Łëäthëř, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš Łëäthëř bëïňğ řëfïňëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning13_Description">[[Ŷöü hävë łëäřňëd thë äbïłïtŷ tö třäčk ňëäřbŷ łäřğë přëdätöřš, šüčh äš Bëäřš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning14_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł ät Škïňňïňğ ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Ŷöü ňöw škïň äňïmäł čäřčäššëš šłïğhtłŷ fäštëř. ]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillSkinning15_Description">[[MÄŠTËŘ ŠKÏŇŇÏŇĞ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Hïdë fřöm ËXQÜÏŠÏTË HÏDË. Ŷöü ňöw hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ËXQÜÏŠÏTË HÏDË whëň ŷöü ğäthëř ït. Whëň řëfïňïňğ Łëäthëř, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš Łëäthëř bëïňğ řëfïňëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting1_Description">[[ŘÜDÏMËŇTÄŘŶ WËÄVÏŇĞ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Łïňëň. Ŷöü hävë dëvëłöpëd ä šïxth šëňšë föř ëdïbłë płäňtš, ëňäbłïňğ ŷöü tö dëtëčt ňëäřbŷ häřvëštäbłë fööd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting2_Description">[[Ŷöüř šëňšë öf šmëłł ïmpřövëš šïğňïfïčäňtłŷ, ëňäbłïňğ ŷöü tö dëtëčt ÄŁČHËMŶ PŁÄŇTŠ fřöm šömë dïštäňčë äwäŷ. ÄŁČHËMŶ PŁÄŇTŠ wïłł ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting3_Description">[[ČÖŇVËŇTÏÖŇÄŁ WËÄVÏŇĞ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Šätëëň. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Häřvëštëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Whëň üšïňğ ä šïčkłë, ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř möřë řëšöüřčëš fřöm płäňtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting4_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Häřvëštëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Whëň üšïňğ ä šïčkłë, ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř płäňtš šłïğhtłŷ fäštëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting5_Description">[[ÄPPŘËŇTÏČË HÄŘVËŠTËŘ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Fïbëřš fřöm ÜŇČÖMMÖŇ FÏBËŘŠ. Ŷöü hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ÜŇČÖMMÖŇ FÏBËŘŠ whëň ŷöü ğäthëř thëm. Whëň řëfïňïňğ čłöth, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš čłöth bëïňğ řëfïňëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting6_Description">[[Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Šïłk. Ŷöüř ëŷëš ğřöw möřë këëň, ëňäbłïňğ ŷöü tö dëtëčt ÄŁČHËMŶ ŠTÖŇËŠ fřöm šömë dïštäňčë äwäŷ. ÄŁČHËMŶ ŠTÖŇËŠ wïłł ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Häřvëštëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Whëň üšïňğ ä šïčkłë, ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř šłïğhtłŷ möřë řëšöüřčëš fřöm płäňtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting7_Description">[[ČÖMPŁËX WËÄVÏŇĞ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Šïłk. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Häřvëštëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Whëň üšïňğ ä šïčkłë, ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř płäňtš šłïğhtłŷ fäštëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting8_Description">[[Ŷöüř ëäřš ğřöw möřë šëňšïtïvë, ëňäbłïňğ ŷöü tö dëtëčt ÄŁČHËMŶ ČŘËÄTÜŘËŠ fřöm šömë dïštäňčë äwäŷ. ÄŁČHËMŶ ČŘËÄTÜŘËŠ wïłł ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting9_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Häřvëštëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Whëň üšïňğ ä šïčkłë, ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř möřë řëšöüřčëš fřöm płäňtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting10_Description">[[ÏŇTŘÏČÄTË WËÄVÏŇĞ: Ŷöü ğäïň thë kňöwłëdğë tö řëfïňë Ïňfüšëd Šïłk. Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Häřvëštëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Whëň üšïňğ ä šïčkłë, ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř płäňtš šłïğhtłŷ fäštëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting11_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Häřvëštëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö mäkë thë möšt öf whät ŷöü ğäthëř. Whëň üšïňğ ä šïčkłë, ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř möřë řëšöüřčëš fřöm płäňtš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting12_Description">[[JÖÜŘŇËŶMÄŇ HÄŘVËŠTËŘ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷdäŷ Fïbëřš fřöm ŘÄŘË FÏBËŘŠ. Ŷöü hävë šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ŘÄŘË FÏBËŘŠ whëň ŷöü ğäthëř thëm. Whëň řëfïňïňğ Łëäthëř, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš Łëäthëř bëïňğ řëfïňëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting13_Description">[[Ŷöüř kňöwłëdğë öf Ňëw Wöřłd Hëmp häš ğřöwň tö thë pöïňt öf ŷöü bëïňğ äbłë tö dëtëčt ït whëň ït ïš ňëäřbŷ. Hëmp Płäňtš ňöw äppëäř öň ŷöüř čömpäšš.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting14_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä Häřvëštëř ïňčřëäšëš, äš döëš ŷöüř äbïłïtŷ tö ütïłïžë thë tööłš öf ŷöüř třädë. Whëň üšïňğ ä šïčkłë, ŷöü ňöw ğäthëř płäňtš šłïğhtłŷ fäštëř.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillHarvesting15_Description">[[MÄŠTËŘ HÄŘVËŠTËŘ: Ŷöü hävë bëğüň tö łëäřň tö dïščëřň ňöřmäł, ëvëřŷ däŷ Fïbëřš fřöm ËXQÜÏŠÏTË FÏBËŘŠ. Ŷöü hävë ä šmäłł čhäňčë tö fïňd ËXQÜÏŠÏTË FÏBËŘŠ whëň ŷöü ğäthëř thëm. Whëň řëfïňïňğ Łëäthëř, ŷöü wäštë łëšš, řëšüłtïňğ ïň böňüš Łëäthëř bëïňğ řëfïňëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing1_Description">[[Řëdüčëš thë ŘËŠÖÜŘČËŠ ŘËQÜÏŘËD TÖ ŘËPÄÏŘ ïtëmš bŷ 5%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing2_Description">[[Řëdüčëš ŁÖŠŠ TÖ MÄXÏMÜM DÜŘÄBÏŁÏTŶ whëň řëpäïřïňğ äň ïtëm bŷ 10%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing3_Description">[[Řëdüčëš thë ŘËŠÖÜŘČËŠ ŘËQÜÏŘËD TÖ ŘËPÄÏŘ ïtëmš bŷ 8%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing4_Description">[[Řëdüčëš thë ŘËŠÖÜŘČËŠ ŘËQÜÏŘËD TÖ ŘËPÄÏŘ ïtëmš bŷ 10%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing5_Description">[[Řëdüčëš ŁÖŠŠ TÖ MÄXÏMÜM DÜŘÄBÏŁÏTŶ whëň řëpäïřïňğ äň ïtëm bŷ äň äddïtïöňäł 15%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing6_Description">[[Řëdüčëš thë ŘËŠÖÜŘČËŠ ŘËQÜÏŘËD TÖ ŘËPÄÏŘ ïtëmš bŷ äň äddïtïöňäł 10%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing7_Description">[[Řëdüčëš thë ŘËŠÖÜŘČËŠ ŘËQÜÏŘËD TÖ ŘËPÄÏŘ ïtëmš bŷ äň äddïtïöňäł 12%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing8_Description">[[Řëdüčëš ŁÖŠŠ TÖ MÄXÏMÜM DÜŘÄBÏŁÏTŶ whëň řëpäïřïňğ äň ïtëm bŷ äň äddïtïöňäł 25%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing9_Description">[[Řëdüčëš thë ŘËŠÖÜŘČËŠ ŘËQÜÏŘËD TÖ ŘËPÄÏŘ ïtëmš bŷ äň äddïtïöňäł 15%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeSkillRepairing10_Description">[[Řëdüčëš ŁÖŠŠ TÖ MÄXÏMÜM DÜŘÄBÏŁÏTŶ whëň řëpäïřïňğ äň ïtëm bŷ äň äddïtïöňäł 30%.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding1_Description">[[ÄPPŘËŇTÏČË ÄŘČHÏTËČT: Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šïğňïfïčäňtłŷ štüřdïëř äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding2_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šłïğhtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding3_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šłïğhtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding4_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šłïğhtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding5_Description">[[JÖÜŘŇËŶMÄŇ ÄŘČHÏČTËČT: Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šïğňïfïčäňtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding6_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šłïğhtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding7_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šłïğhtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding8_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šłïğhtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding9_Description">[[Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šłïğhtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
	<string key="TradeskillBuilding10_Description">[[MÄŠTËŘ ÄŘČHÏTËČT: Ŷöüř škïłł äš ä büïłdëř ğřöwš. Štřüčtüřëš thät ŷöü büïłd äřë ňöw šïğňïfïčäňtłŷ štüřdïëř thäň bëföřë äňd čäň šüštäïň möřë dämäğë bëföřë fäłłïňğ. Öňłŷ ňëw štřüčtüřëš äřë äffëčtëd.]]</string>
</resources>

